A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (A-K) FA1783
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts, 2007-2019; 3; 21.65 Cubic Feet 57 letter document boxes
  - Borscht Corporation - Film Festival (2012-0238), 2011-2012 (Box 16, Folder 217)
  - Bragg Jam, Inc. - Sustaining Bragg Jam (2017-54795) (Box 16, Folder 224)
  - Bragg Jam, Inc. - Second Sundays (2016-52603) (Box 16, Folder 225)
    Free monthly outdoor concert series in the College Hill neighborhood.
  - Brandon Gardner - PraiseFest (2016-52675), 2013-2016 (Box 16, Folder 227)
  - Bridge Red - Bridge Red Studios Project Space, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0329), 2008-2012 (Box 17, Folder 232)
  - BRITDOC Inc. - Good Pitch Miami 2017 (2016-53324) (Box 17, Folder 233)
  - The Brothers Network - Multidisciplinary Festival Featuring Black Male Choreographers, Filmmakers, Actors, Writers, and Composers, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-4627), 2011-2013 (Box 17, Folder 237)
  - Broward County Film Society - The Florida Prize (2015-51538), 2016 (Box 17, Folder 239)
    Award presented at the Fort Lauderdale International Film Festival to an outstanding local film professional.
  - Cannonball Miami - Strategic Planning (2012-0356), 2010-2012 (Box 18, Folder 249)
  - Carnegie Institute - Muse: Your Friendly Cultural Companion (2017-54137) (Box 18, Folder 251)
  - Caroline Calouche and Co. - First Annual Show at Romare Bearden Park (2016-52629) (Box 18, Folder 254)
  - CAST Education, Inc. - Growth and Development (2013-46355), 2007-2013 (Box 19, Folder 257)
  - Catzie Vilayphonh - Lao-American Storytelling Workshop, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0073), 2011-2014 (Box 19, Folder 259)
  - Center for Applied Theater and Active Culture - The Devil's Milk Trilogy (2014-50157), 2014-2015 (Box 19, Folder 268)
  - Ceramic League of Miami - Center for Ceramics Workshop, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-2173), 2009-2014 (Box 21, Folder 287)
  - Chamber Music Silicon Valley - Common Sounds (2017-55020) (Box 21, Folder 290)
  - Chamber Music Society of Detroit - "inDepth" Concert Series (2012-0240), 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 291)
  - Charlotte Black Film Festival - Film Festival (2016-52724), 2013-2016 (Box 21, Folder 293)
  - Charlotte Center for Literary Arts, Inc. - 4x4CLT: Poetry in Public Spaces (2016-52697), 2016-2017 (Box 21, Folder 294)
  - Charlotte Film Society, Inc. - Film Lab Series (2016-52665), 2013-2016 (Box 22, Folder 295)
  - Charlotte Symphony Orchestra Society - Brahms v. Radiohead (2016-52685) (Box 22, Folder 298)
  - Charlotte Symphony Orchestra Society - KnightSounds Concert Series (2012-0309), 2010-2013 (Box 22, Folder 300)
  - Chez Bushwick, Inc. - Three-Year Artists' Residency (2012-0101), 2010-2015 (Box 22, Folder 302)
    Collaborations between Chez Bushwick found director Jonah Bokaer and Miami-raised sculptor and conceptual artist Daniel Arsham at the Adrienne Arsht Center.
  - Chicken and Egg Pictures - Accelerator Lab (2017-54344) (Box 23, Folder 312)
  - Children's Theatre of Charlotte Inc. - Director Residency Program (2015-50840), 2015-2016 (Box 23, Folder 313)
  - Cineques Inc. - Audience Favorite Feature and Audience Favorite Documentary Awards (2012-0181), 2009-2013 (Box 23, Folder 319)
  - CINTAS Foundation - Visual Arts Fellowship (2014-49383), 2014-2017 (Box 23, Folder 320)
  - City Lights Performance Group of San Jose - City Lights Theater (2017-54792) (Box 23, Folder 326)
  - City Lights Performance Group of San Jose - Immersive Frankenstein (2016-52689) (Box 23, Folder 327)
  - City of Akron - Downtown Akron Summer Event Series 2015 (2015-50974) (Box 24, Folder 330)
  - City of Akron - Downtown Akron Summer Event Series (2013-46697), 2011-2013 (Box 24, Folder 331)
  - City of Miami - Haitian Heritage Art Project, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0331), 2010-2015 (Box 25, Folder 349)
  - City Theatre - Building the Wall (2017-54899) (Box 26, Folder 366)
  - City Theatre - CityWrights Professional Weekend for Playwrights (2014-49378) (Box 26, Folder 367)
  - Classical South Florida - Concierto (2013-45991), 2011-2013 (Box 27, Folder 384)
    A bilingual classical music program featuring the work of Latino musicians.
  - Cleveland International Film Festival Inc. - Knight and Day in Akron Film Festival (2016-53493), 2016-2017 (Box 27, Folder 387)
  - College for Creative Studies, Detroit - Culture Lab 2015 and 2016 (2014-50072), 2014-2016 (Box 28, Folder 401)
  - The Commons - Concert Series (2015-50817) (Box 29, Folder 409)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Knight Detroit Young Musicians of Color Fund (2012-2030), 2011-2016 (Box 30, Folder 432)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall, Knight Foundation Digital Innovation Fund (2012-0216), 2012-2016 (Box 30, Folder 433)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Arab Community Center for Economic and Social Services (2012-0217), 2012-2017 (Box 31, Folder 434-435)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Michigan Opera Theatre (2012-0218), 2012-2017 (Box 31, Folder 436)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Knight Detroit Museum Fund (2012-0219), 2012-2016 (Box 31, Folder 437)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Knight Detroit Children's Book Fair Fund (2012-0221), 2012-2016 (Box 31, Folder 438)
  - Community Hall Foundation, Inc. - Arts and Culture in Summit County (2015-50613) (Box 35, Folder 468)
  - Community Hall Foundation, Inc. - Audience Outreach Project (2013-46706), 2011-2014 (Box 35, Folder 469)
  - Community Television Foundation of South Florida, Television Station WPBT - Local Arts Content (2012-3572), 2011-2013 (Box 35, Folder 476)
  - Coral Gables Cinemateque - Programming and Educational Outreach (2012-0376), 2012-2015 (Box 36, Folder 485)
  - Coral Gables Cinemateque - Programming and Educational Outreach (2012-0393), 2011-2012 (Box 36, Folder 486)
  - Coral Gables Community Foundation - General Fundraising Campaign (2016-53432) (Box 36, Folder 487)
  - Coral Morphologic - Aqua/Cultural Transformations: A Multi-Media Coral Reef in Museum Park, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0333), 2010-2012 (Box 36, Folder 488)
  - The Corporation of Mercer University - Collaborative Efficiencies (2017-54945) (Box 36, Folder 492)
  - Creative City Collaborative of Delray Beach - Arts Garage: 2012 Knight Arts Challenge People's Choice Award (2013-45063) (Box 38, Folder 516)
  - Creative Many Michigan Inc. - St. Etienne France Biennale (2017-53841) (Box 38, Folder 519)
  - Cuban Museum Inc. - Azaceta Exhibition (2014-50174), 2014-2015 (Box 39, Folder 527)
  - Cuban Museum Inc. - Sweet Home Museo Cubano, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0334), 2011-2014 (Box 39, Folder 528)
  - Culture Lab Detroit - Post-Truth Art/Beauty in Transition (2017-54037) (Box 39, Folder 530)
  - CultureWorks Greater Philadelphia - Venture Program: An Arts Accelerator (2016-52669) (Box 39, Folder 531)
  - CultureWorks Greater Philadelphia - Filadelfia Latin American Film Festival (2014-48719) (Box 39, Folder 533)
  - Dance USA - Knight Dance Initiative Convening (2017-54222), 2015-2017 (Box 40, Folder 544)
  - Darla Jackson - Philadelphia Sculpture Gym, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0050), 2010-2012 (Box 40, Folder 545)
  - David Guinn - Freewall: the Artists' Wall (2012-3078), 2011-2014 (Box 40, Folder 551)
  - Detroit Educational Television Foundation - Book View Now Coverage of the 2016 Miami Book Fair International (2016-53255) (Box 41, Folder 567)
  - The Detroit Institute of Arts - Inside Out Nationwide Launch Oversight (2014-49510), 2012-2016 (Box 41, Folder 571)
  - The Detroit Institute of Arts - The Lumin Experience (2017-54065) (Box 41, Folder 572)
  - The Detroit Institute of Arts - Inside Out Detroit (2016-53562), 2016-2017 (Box 41, Folder 573)
  - Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall, Inc. - League 2017 National Conference: DSO Activities (2017-53914) (Box 42, Folder 579)
  - Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall, Inc. - Technology at the Max: Feasibility Consultant and Experiment (2017-52004) (Box 42, Folder 580)
  - Diaspora Vibe Cultural Arts Incubator - Artists-in-Residency (2016-53610) (Box 43, Folder 586)
  - Dimensions Variable - 2015 Exhibitions (2015-50915) (Box 43, Folder 593)
  - Dimensions Variable - Site-Specific Works, Lecture and Discussion Series, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0335), 2010-2014 (Box 43, Folder 594)
  - District One Community Education Center Inc. - Dance Africa Philadelphia, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0051), 2010-2013 (Box 44, Folder 597)
  - Doner Studio, LLC - Book of Artworks by Michele Oka Doner (2015-51463), 2013-2015 (Box 44, Folder 604)
  - Drexel University - Science of Music (2012-3401), 2011-2016 (Box 44, Folder 606)
  - Downtown Choir Parents Association - New World School of the Arts Choir Performance (2015-51495) (Box 44, Folder 609)
  - Eastern Market Corporation - Murals in the Market Festival 17-19 (2017-54444) (Box 46, Folder 627)
  - Edge Zones - Miami Performance Festival 2013 (2012-2126), 2011-2012 (Box 46, Folder 631)
  - Ekonomisk Management - Mozart in Havana: Simone Dinnerstien and the Havana Lyceum Orchestra (2017-53924) (Box 46, Folder 632)
  - Erica Hawthorne - Art Production Costs, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0109), 2011-2017 (Box 47, Folder 648)
  - Exchange for Change - Knight Art Champion 2017 Designation: P. Scott Cunningham (2017-55373) (Box 47, Folder 653)
  - Exhibition District - 100 Block Mural Project (2016-52746) (Box 47, Folder 656)
  - The Fabric Workshop and Museum - A Tactile Bidding, Ann Hamilton (2015-51378) (Box 48, Folder 657)
  - Field Note Stenographers, The 567 Center for Renewal - Diggin' the Field (2016-52696) (Box 48, Folder 670)
  - Firebird Youth Chinese Orchestra - Master Class (2016-52720) (Box 48, Folder 671)
  - Firebird Youth Chinese Orchestra - Outreach (2013-46755) (Box 49, Folder 672)
  - Florida Grand Opera - Unexpected Opera in Unexpected Places, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0336), 2010-2015 (Box 49, Folder 678)
  - Florida International University Foundation Inc. - CasaCuba Executive Director Search and Salary (2017-54219) (Box 49, Folder 681)
  - Florida International University Foundation Inc. - Knight Art Champion 2017 Designation, Michelle Oka Donner (2017-55381) (Box 50, Folder 688)
  - Florida International University - Knight Fellows in Creative Writing, Knight Arts Challenge (2010-0256), 2008-2014 (Box 50, Folder 689)
  - Foundation for Detroit's Future - Cost Sharing of the DIA Observer (2016-53664), 2016-2017 (Box 50, Folder 704)
  - Foundation for New Education Initiatives - Carl Hiaason, Knight Art Champion 2017 Designation (2017-55377) (Box 53, Folder 726)
  - Fountainhead Residency - Fountainhead Residency (2017-54260), 2014-2017 (Box 53, Folder 728)
  - Frank Falestra - Experimental Music Event, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0381), 2011-2015 (Box 53, Folder 733)
  - Franklin's Paine Skatepark Fund - Turn Blacktop Lots into Art-Laden Skate Parks, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0078), 2010-2014 (Box 53, Folder 734)
  - Fresh Artists - Cool Jobs Career Expo (2014-50062), 2014-2016 (Box 53, Folder 741)
  - Fresh Artists - Fresh Studios, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0053), 2009-2013 (Box 54, Folder 742)
  - Fresh Produce Records - Live Musical Performances (2015-50782), 2013-2015 (Box 54, Folder 743)
  - Friends of the Bass Museum, Inc. - M-7 (2013-46813), 2012-2015 (Box 54, Folder 745)
    Coordinator who will manage collaborative projects between Miami's seven public art museums and leverage their individual collections into a collective cultural resource.
  - Friends of the Douglass Theatre Complex - Douglass Goes Digital (2015-50689) (Box 54, Folder 747)
  - Fundacion Educativa Carlos M. Castaneda, Inc. - Martha Marchena Concert (2014-49346) (Box 55, Folder 753)
  - Fund for Philadelphia - Parks and Recreation's Performing Arts in After School Programs Initiative (2012-2244), 2011-2015 (Box 55, Folder 761)
  - Fund for Philadelphia - City Hall Sings, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0048), 2009-2012 (Box 55, Folder 762)
  - Funding Arts Broward - Knight New Work Award, Knight Arts Challenge (2010-0261), 2009-2013 (Box 56, Folder 767)
  - Gabrielle Lamb and Adam Barruch World Premiere - BalletX (2013-46753), 2012-2013 (Box 56, Folder 770)
  - Gene Knific - Artist Collective Project: Mitten (2016-52382), 2013-2016 (Box 56, Folder 776)
  - Georgia Trust for Historic Preservation - Community Cultural Events (2015-50586) (Box 57, Folder 782)
  - Georiga Trust for Historic Preservation - Hay House Free Events (2014-48801) (Box 57, Folder 783)
  - Glass Art Society, Inc. - Conference in San Jose (2014-50061) (Box 57, Folder 791)
  - Goodyear Arts - Supporting Charlotte Artists (2017-54811) (Box 58, Folder 800)
  - Grantmakers in the Arts - 2017 Conference (2017-53825) (Box 59, Folder 814)
  - Greater Akron Musical Association - Community Production of A Midsummer Nights Dream (2013-46713), 2012-2013 (Box 59, Folder 822)
  - Greater Akron Musical Association - 100th Anniversary Rite of Spring Production (2012-0161), 2010-2012 (Box 59, Folder 823)
  - Greater Philadelphia Chamber of Commerce Regional Foundation - Arts Leader Diversity Scholarships (2016-52718) (Box 59, Folder 827)
  - Greater Philadelphia Cultural Alliance - Big Data Meetups: Using Marketing Technology to Transform Audiences (2016-52667) (Box 59, Folder 828)
  - Greater Philadelphia Cultural Alliance - DNC Broad Street Activation Project (2016-52756), 2014-2016 (Box 59, Folder 829)
  - Guitars Over Guns - Mayor Carlos Gimenez and Andrew Teomanson: Knight Arts Champion 2017 Designation (2017-55375) (Box 60, Folder 839)
  - Haitian Heritage Museum - Digitization and Curation Initiative (2014-48108) (Box 60, Folder 843)
  - Hastings Street Blues Project, LLC - Hastings Street Blues (2014-49988), 2012-2015 (Box 60, Folder 847)
  - Heidi Saman - Namour (2014-50032), 2012-2015 (Box 61, Folder 850)
  - Highland Square Neighborhood Association - PorchRokr (2015-50878), 2015-2016 (Box 61, Folder 854)
    An annual arts and music festival set on the porches and lawns of Akron's Highland Square neighborhood.
  - Historical Association of Southern Florida - Folk Artist-in-Residence Initiative, Knight Arts Challenge (2010-0262), 2008-2012 (Box 61, Folder 863)
  - Inkub8 - Residency Program, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0338), 2009-2013 (Box 63, Folder 893)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art Miami, Inc. - Acquisition of Mark Handforth's Dr. Pepper (2017-55349) (Box 64, Folder 903)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art Miami, Inc. - General Operating Support (2017-54119) (Box 64, Folder 904)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art Miami, Inc. - Charitable Recommendation (Alex Gartenfeld) (2016-52216) (Box 64, Folder 905)
  - Inta Inc. - Eiko and Koma (2012-3567), 2011-2014 (Box 64, Folder 907)
  - Invisible River - Invisible River (2015-50655), 2012-2015 (Box 66, Folder 931)
    Interactive dance perfomance along the banks of the Schuylkill River.
  - Jazz Arts Initiative - Growing Audiences, Charlotte (2017-54814) (Box 67, Folder 936)
  - Jazz Arts Initiative - Jazz Room Series Expansion, Stage Door Theater (2016-52708) (Box 67, Folder 937)
  - Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County, Inc. - Inside Out Year Two (2017-54188) (Box 67, Folder 949)
  - Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County, Inc. - Teresita Fernandez, Knight Art Champion 2017 Designation (2017-55374) (Box 67, Folder 950)
  - Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County, Inc. - Inside Out Pilot Year in Miami (2016-53137) (Box 67, Folder 951)
  - Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County, Inc. - Development Staffing (2016-53194), 2014-2016 (Box 67, Folder 952)
  - Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County, Inc. - Executive Director Search (2015-50536) (Box 67, Folder 953)
  - Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County, Inc. - Curtain, Jonah Bokaer (2015-50585) (Box 67, Folder 954)
  - Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County, Inc. - Scholl Lecture Series (2015-51778) (Box 68, Folder 955)
  - Kang Vang - 1984 (2014-49905), 2012-2015 (Box 68, Folder 960)
    Hmong language/translated. Written and directed by St. Paul filmmaker Kang Vang.
  - Karen Peterson and Dancers Inc. - Inclusive Dance, Benefits for All, Expanding the Boundaries, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0339), 2010-2012 (Box 68, Folder 961)
  - Karen Peterson and Dancers Inc. - The 6th Talent Showcase, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0339), 2012 March 02; 2012 March 09 (Box 68, Folder 961)
  - Kathleen Bonanno - Musehouse: A Center for the Literary Arts, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0056), 2011-2012 (Box 68, Folder 962)
  - Kathleen Hudspeth - Turn-Based Press, Knight Arts Challenge (2009-0181), 2009-2010 (Box 68, Folder 963)
  - Keepers of the Art Education - Music Showcase Concert Series (2016-52589) (Box 68, Folder 965)
  - Keepers of the Art, Inc. - Music and Muse Film Festival (2014-49244), 2012-2015 (Box 68, Folder 966)
    Celebration of "true school" hip-hop and the launch of Muse, a media education film festival.
  - Kent State University Foundation - Traveling Stanzas Presentation at the Forum of Regional Associations of Grantmakers Conference (2017-54359), 2013-2017 (Box 68, Folder 968)
  - Kimmel Center, Inc. - Asphalt Piloten's Tape Riot, Philadelphia International Festival of the Arts (2017-54984) (Box 69, Folder 970)
  - Kimmel Center, Inc. - Underground Residencies (2014-49552), 2012-2015 (Box 69, Folder 971)
  - Kimmel Center, Inc. - Residency Program, Black Box Theater, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0081), 2010-2013 (Box 69, Folder 972)
  - LAB Miami - Art Hackathon, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0383), 2011-2013 (Box 69, Folder 979)
- Technology and Media Innovation, 2012-2018; 4; 14.81 Cubic Feet 39 letter document boxes
  The Technology and Media Innovation program focuses on investing in technology that impacts the way people interact with news and information. This program area overlaps with the Journalism and Media Innovation program but was referred to as "Technology and Media Innovation" during the time of the grants in this collection.
  - Akron Art Museum - Building Data Capacity (2017-53837), 2017-2018 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Allied Media Projects, Inc. - Detroit Community Technology Project (2016-53141), 2014-2017 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    Digital Stewards Network's neighborhood-level training programs to help increase internet access.
  - Alison Macrina - Library Freedom Project (2014-50256), 2015-2017 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Asian American Journalists Association - Ballot.fyi (2017-55212) (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Bad Idea Factory - The Glorious Contextubot (2017-54396) (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - The Barnes Foundation - Visual Collections Browser (2017-53836) (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Bay Area Video Coalition, Inc. - QCTools 1.0 (2016-52532), 2013-2016 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Beneficent Technology, Inc. - AuthentIcon: Easy Visual Fingerprint Identification (2015-51982) (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Ben Sax - Perceptoscope: Augmented Reality (2015-50767), 2013-2015 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University - Putting Civic Online Reasoning in Civics Class (2017-54413) (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University - Law, Order and Algorithms: Making Sense of 100 Million Highway Patrol Stops (2016-52100), 2016-2017 (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University - d.school's Human-Centered Design Methods and Tools (2014-49422), 2013-2017 (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - Bouldin Labs - IdeaMapr (2015-51649), 2013-2017 (Box 16, Folder 219)
    Tool to help communities understand complex civic decisions.
  - BRITDOC Inc. - Engaging Communities with Documentary (2014-48915), 2013-2014 (Box 17, Folder 234)
  - Brooklyn Public Library - TeleStory: Library Based Video Visitation for Children of Incarcerated Parents (2016-52938), 2012-2017 (Box 17, Folder 236)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - MetroLab Roundtable Series on Instrumentation (2017-54364) (Box 18, Folder 255)
  - Catherine Bracy - Spectogram Tool for Public Input (2015-52009), 2013-2015 (Box 19, Folder 258)
  - CEL Education Fund - Coworker.org: Civic Infrastructure for Workers (2015-51991), 2014-2016 (Box 19, Folder 264)
  - Center for Responsive Politics - Journalist Access to Campaign Finance Information (2015-51019), 2013-2016 (Box 20, Folder 277)
  - Center for Technology and Civic Life - Civic Engagement Toolkit (2015-51059), 2015-2016 (Box 20, Folder 278)
  - Charlotte Area Transit System - ZipBus (2015-52008) (Box 21, Folder 292)
  - Christian Milneil - News Inequality Project (2017-54379) (Box 23, Folder 315)
  - City of Akron - ASCITI: Akron Smart City IoT Technology Initiative (2017-54435) (Box 23, Folder 328)
  - City of Boston - Beta Blocks (2017-54371) (Box 24, Folder 332)
  - City of Boston - Open Data to Open Knowledge (2015-50349), 2014-2016 (Box 24, Folder 333)
  - City of Detroit - Connected Infrastructure for Detroit (2017-54432) (Box 24, Folder 342)
  - City of Miami - Resilience Data Roadmap for IoT Innovation (2017-54431) (Box 25, Folder 348)
  - City of Philadelphia - Road Mapping an Actionable Strategy for Philadelphia's Smart Initiative (2017-54433) (Box 25, Folder 350)
  - City of Raleigh - Democratizing Data through Visual Search Results (2015-51998) (Box 25, Folder 351)
  - City of San Jose - Digital Inclusion and Broadband Strategy: Internet of Things Applications (2017-54434) (Box 25, Folder 359)
  - ClearGov Inc. - Municipal Benchmarking (2015-51648), 2013-2015 (Box 27, Folder 385)
  - Cloudstitch Inc. - Mass-Producing, Customizing, and Reusing News Interactives without Programming (2014-50229), 2012-2015 (Box 27, Folder 388)
    Web platform to help non-programmers rapidly create, modify, and publish interactive data displays.
  - Code for Charlotte - Citygram (2015-51650), 2013-2015 (Box 28, Folder 395)
    A geographically-relevant notifications platform powered by open data.
  - Code for Science and Society - The Dat Project (2017-54996) (Box 28, Folder 396)
  - Code for Science and Society, Max Ogden - PublicBits: Breaking Down Open Data Silos (2015-51933), 2013-2016 (Box 28, Folder 393)
  - Community Foundation of New Jersey - Legislation Tracker: Beyond the Bills (2015-51997), 2015-2016 (Box 33, Folder 453)
  - Community Partners - OpenNews Transition (2016-53554), 2016-2017 (Box 35, Folder 471)
  - CommunityRED - ADAPT Game (2014-49643), 2012-2014 (Box 35, Folder 473)
    Mobile game to help journalists assess digital threats, risks, and vulnerabilities.
  - Crisis Text Line - Phase Three Growth (2016-52758), 2014-2017 (Box 38, Folder 520)
  - Crisis Text Line - Phase Two Growth (2015-50353), 2015-2017 (Box 38, Folder 521)
  - Crisis Text Line - Young People of Color Mental Health Initiative (2016-53177), 2014-2017 (Box 38, Folder 523)
  - Crisis Text Line - Young People of Color Mental Health Initiative (2015-51387) (Box 38, Folder 524)
  - CTC Technology and Energy - Broadband Coalition for Libraries (2015-52013), 2013-2015 (Box 38, Folder 525)
  - CTY - Numia: Measuring Multimodal Active Transit in St. Louis (2015-50764), 2013-2015 (Box 38, Folder 526)
  - DailyCloudt, Inc. - Billcam (2015-51672), 2013-2015 (Box 39, Folder 542)
  - Dan Archer (Erin Polgreen) - Ketla: Mobile News Comics (2014-50232), 2012-2015 (Box 39, Folder 543)
  - Datascope Analytics LLC - Scrubadub (2015-51256) (Box 40, Folder 547)
    A tool to enable FOIA officers to accelerate the process of releasing documents while maintaining privacy for individuals referenced in the text.
  - Data and Society Research Institute - Media Engagement and Outreach (2017-54817), 2015-2017 (Box 40, Folder 549)
  - Data and Society Research Institute - Empowering the Public to Understand the Societal Implications of Data-Driven Technologies (2015-51995), 2014-2016 (Box 40, Folder 550)